What's the deal with airplane peanuts?
>> From bonding over their childhoods in
New York City. And if you know anything
about this stand, this it reminds me of
what New York used to be. The city used
to be run by overweight criminals. Yes.
To going on story wars alongside Dan
Soder.
>> This is definitely Chris or Tim who had
present fathers.
>> No, but there's this story saying that
is the father wasn't there.
>> Fell down the stairs on the way to the
hospital.
By the way, I didn't realize you were
reading it. I thought you were just
admitting it.
>> No, I was like,
>> and all the times Tim Dylan has appeared
on Chrissy Chaos.
>> Very good point. She does. All I do is
make good points.
>> I want a sandwich so bad I kill someone.
>> This video contains all of the funniest
moments between Tim Dylan and Chris
Stephano. Starting off with the time Tim
met TT Jerry.
>> Hello, my darling.
>> You want to come on?
>> Look at this. We got a special guest
Halloween dropping.
Tim Dylan dropped it.
>> It's the I call this the fat racist
pumpkin.
>> And it's it's a pumpkin who likes other
groups but realizes we all have to just
slow down a little.
>> Yeah.
>> You look gorgeous, by the way. You look
stunning.
>> And um
>> it's um it's it's a pumpkin. We were
just been talking about Kanye West. How
Kanye West called President Biden.
>> Yeah. He's having a week. Kanye's having
a week. Um,
>> Jerry said that she's attracted to Kanye
West and and his new work and the new
Kanye West.
>> There's something about a man who will
burn it all down. Right. Right. That's
right.
>> She likes that about it cuz she was just
telling us her boyfriend Scar, who just
recently got out of prison, has been
calling her only for booty calls and she
doesn't want that. She said, she goes,
"I want an intelligent man like Kanye
West. Intelligent black man." And
>> you know,
>> have you ever had a woman call you just
for booty talk? like,
>> well, well,
>> they had to fix the air conditioner
units in my house and one of the guys
went up there, Guatemalan guy went up
there and fell through my attic ceiling,
right? Fell on the floor. Whole thing,
blah, blah, blah, blah, blah. All of a
sudden, the foreman calls me. He goes,
"Yeah, my guys his neck hurts now." All
of a sudden, his neck is hurting. Trying
to look for some cash. So, TTJ Jerry
being a career criminal goes up to that
room and says, "Oh, you know, your neck
hurts." And the guy says, "See, see?"
And he goes, "Uh, he goes, "Well, do you
have your papers? I just want to know if
you have your papers. And then and then
so and then the guy was like, "No paper.
No paper." And he goes, "Yeah." He goes,
"So then go back up on the ladder and
fix the ceiling."
>> [__] yeah.
>> So you would think that
>> TT
>> TT and I I wasn't there. This was all
told secondhand to me, of course.
>> But but I but I believe that it happened
that way and that ceiling was fixed and
everything was fine. And then a ring
went missing. Somebody stole a ring.
>> Oh. So, they were going to come, you
know, we had it was a big thing and TT
Jerry just flat out said, "If I don't
get that ring back, I'm going to go to
immigration and I'm going to make sure
this guy gets deported." And then guess
what? About an hour later, the ring was
left on a paint can outside the house.
So, sometimes you have
>> This is the pilot of the sitcom. I want
you to go in and I want you to pitch
this. And so, this is the resolution of
the pilot. my Puerto Rican transgender
somewhat Republican uh uncle aunt
>> uh goes and threatens to inform on the
paperless undocumented worker and gets
the ring back.
>> Yeah.
>> End of episode one. Who's in
>> Yeah. Well, how about And it was it was
it was fireworks.
>> But this is the way real life is. Start
making real life. Stop making Fire
Island. You got to make which by the way
it's a mo and god bless everyone but the
movie is about gay guys who go to an
island to [__] for a week and somehow
have a bad time. Yeah.
>> Somehow it's bad to me. It's just funny
the idea of making a film about going to
a paradise. Right.
>> Which is what Fire Island is,
>> right?
>> And then why are you looking up
Firefest? He's so dumb. He's so dumb.
He's looking up Firefest right now.
We're talking about a movie called Fire
Island. He's looking up Firefest. Do you
realize what I deal with? Do you
understand how how hard it is for me and
how impressive it is I've gotten
anywhere with this with this dead
weight? I carry just dead weight. You
know, I said to Ben, my my producer, we
were eating.
>> Who's on the hot seat?
>> Yeah, he's on the hot seat. Better he
better figure it out.
>> Yeah, cuz almost Pimp's coming.
>> Pimp's coming. I'm going to take Pimp
and I'm not going to pay you, but you're
going to meet Whitney Cummings. So, the
whole thing is you're going to inject
the Botox into Whitney Cummings ass.
Here's the whole thing. And it's better
than money. So the reality
>> we're going to we're going to release
this. So we got
>> I don't care. She doesn't care. She's a
comic.
>> Okay. She's the only comic in LA right
now, not in jail. RP. You literally
don't have the rights you think you
have.
>> That's what I'm saying.
>> When defending yourself, specifically
your home. In states like Florida and
Texas, you can pretty much get rid of
them,
>> right?
>> In states like New York and California,
they'll be like, "Okay, well, what were
they doing that was threatening?" It's
like, "They're in my [__] house." And
they're like, "Yeah, but past that."
>> Yeah.
>> Were they doing anything that bothered
you? It's like they're in my house where
my kids sleep. Yeah, we get it. But were
they like being mean? Like
>> so you would have to get a really good
lawyer in New York or LA as opposed to
like in Texas if somebody comes in your
house peacefully for a dinner party. You
can kill them.
>> You're allowed to kill them. If they
come in and they're peacefully and they
say something you dislike, you're
allowed to take their life and move on.
I love gulab jamun, which is an Indian
little uh doughut that spits uh it spits
like uh syrup.
>> Okay.
>> Um because have you ever had gulab
jamun?
>> I I thought there was the new DA of New
York.
>> Yeah.
>> What was a better time in New York City
history specifically than the 80s and
the '90s when it was fully run by the
mob. It should be and it should be and
you know people there was very there I
know in amongst the mobsters I get that
I I understand one side of that but in
the neighborhoods where the mobsters
live no crime no problems everybody was
okay
>> well they they have a monopoly on the
crime
>> but but they're not committing crime
again your mom could walk down the
street and that's what I like about the
stand they're not robbing everyone in
the neighborhood they're robbing us what
it is
>> they're robbing the people that walk
into the building so that's what I like
not like they're not just grabbing an
old lady they're like no no come to a
Oh, here. Where's the money?
>> No, no. Jim Dylan's making some cash
now. Let's squeeze him. Let's get him.
>> Let's get the sword swallowing. He won't
even notice.
>> I get it. And I appreciate it. I like
it.
>> Yeah. You're always going like,
>> I don't even know. There's so many rooms
here. There's people. I don't know what
any of them do.
>> Nobody. I have no idea what any of them
are doing.
>> They don't know what they're doing.
>> I don't know what they're doing. I just
know I'm getting an invoice every week
and I'm paying it off and I don't know
what they're doing. There's people
There's women just sitting there eating
salad quietly and going back to work.
>> It's what it is. I don't know what they
could be doing. I I haven't performed at
the stand in 3 years, but yet I've been
advertised every week.
>> So, that's just what it is. You just pay
the people just deal with it.
>> It's old school.
>> It's just old school. You got to respect
that. And then and then Chris looks at
me and says, "Why don't you come do his
podcast?" And guess what? I did it here.
>> It's smart.
>> This is definitely Chris or Tim who had
present fathers.
>> This story saying that is the father
wasn't there.
>> My father fell down the stairs on the
way to the hospital. I don't even know
what that means. while my mother was
giving birth to me and broke my
>> By the way, I didn't realize you were
reading it. I thought you were just
admitting it.
>> No, no, no. I was like,
>> I really don't know how the game is
playing.
>> Tim, what are you doing?
>> No, but here's what I'm trying to
understand. So, the father isn't at the
hospital while the woman's [__] two
legs broken.
>> Yeah. I mean, the guy had two broken
legs. I don't know. He's in the hospital
>> or he or he knuckles it there and he
deserves that world's greatest dad bug.
Yeah.
>> Or me.
>> Or no. How about it could be Louis and
Jay because what if that's the mother
told them?
>> Oh yeah. Can you Can you tell us when
your dad was stabbed?
>> My dad was stabbed when I was four years
old.
>> Yeah.
>> I'm sorry to hear that.
>> He might have been So he might have
>> murdered.
>> And Well, did he could Let me ask you
this. Could he not run away cuz he had
broken legs?
>> Yeah, that's why.
>> Is that why he was killed?
>> That's how he gives it up. He goes, "No,
his run was a little wobbly because of
his legs. didn't fall down the stairs.
Someone broke his legs. Someone years.
>> Maybe it's Chris's dad cuz he was some
gambling dad.
>> Some Italian.
>> And now he lied to Chris and he's like,
"Oh, I fell down the stairs." And Chris
is like, "Did you though?" That's what
it is.
>> That's a story my mother. Also, uh, the
Jets didn't cover.
>> Yeah, I remember your birthday cuz the
Jets didn't cover and, uh, I broke my
legs on the way to the hospital.
>> No, dude. My My father's he was there. I
feel like if this was Dan or Jay, I
would have heard this story.
>> That was a happy hour. Yeah, you know
where he was.
>> I I I would have heard this story. Dan,
was your was your father in the hospital
when you were born?
>> No,
>> he wasn't. He really wasn't.
>> He was happy.
>> I was kidding.
>> I'm not.
>> I think it's Lewis. I'm telling you
right now.
>> [__] Ah [__]
>> I kind of family couldn't afford stairs.
>> There's no way they
>> because I think it's something his mom
told him in
>> a shot.
>> No, Lewis definitely lived in door to
lawn.
We
>> I lived in a basement apartment. You
can't fall off the stairs.
>> Oh, Chris or Tim. Chris or Tim. Chris or
Tim?
>> I thought it was Lewis because I think
you're so good at this.
>> Oh, God. That that smile's dreamy. I
can't I have to believe him.
>> Christ is handsome.
>> Look away, Louis.
>> You know me.
>> Chris, is it you?
>> Uh uh.
>> Oh, I can I can It's honestly not. That
would be funny if it was. You don't
think I would have You don't think you
would have heard I've told every story
about my father. I don't have any more
material.
>> That's it.
>> I'm My final vote is Tim Dylan. I saw
Tim smirk. I feel like he was trying to
hide something.
>> Son of a [__] I can't pull mine back.
>> Here it is. Tim Dylan. Final answer.
Alex, all of our answers. Right.
>> That story belongs to Chrissy Diaz.
>> Even the other day I was in the
Hamptons. Let me tell you right now. Let
me tell you right now, people. There is
violence. There is violence in the
Hamptons. be there's violence and it's
scary because I found out someone that
lives on my block is a firefighter.
>> Okay,
>> this is what I mean.
>> Yes,
>> this is what I mean. When you let the
blue collar in,
>> okay, it's a real big problem for me
because it's just opening the door to
sanitation workers and then God help us
cos and then criminals.
>> It's a thing. You go blue collar, blue
club and then there's criminals right
here. Yeah. Yeah. So, firefighters like,
"Oh, big 911 guy." Nah, you go right
there as criminal. So, I feel very
comfortable with like private equity,
hedge funds.
>> Uh, inherited money. Yeah.
>> But once we start getting into like I
work on a truck.
>> No.
>> Very nervous. I get very nervous when
people start working on trucks.
>> Yeah. You don't even want them to come
into Suffach County. You want them to
You go as far as
>> I want to be the only piece of [__] in
my neighborhood. I want to get all the
scorn. I want to be the only guy that
looks like this in my neighborhood. I
want everyone else to hate me.
>> Beverly Hills is in the geographical
city of LA, but it's not really a part
of LA from the from the government point
of view. They have their own little
ecosystem.
>> Part of the LA County.
>> It's like the Vatican. That's right. In
a way, it's part of LA. Just scroll
down.
>> Do you think West Hollywood knows that
it's just a FLLA of Beverly Hills?
>> Yeah.
>> Beverly Hills probably looks at West
Hollywood like a flla. I think I think
um
West Hollywood is where you would would
go if to just get your stuck.
>> Yeah. Right. It's what it is, right?
Which a lot of these probably shots do.
They they go out a little bit, go down a
little sunset, and they just get a
little sucked. Come right back.
>> It's actually not gay. Yeah. It's
actually not gay.
>> It's called It's called It's called
owning a company.
>> It's called having a friend.
>> It's what it is. Does Tim survive
prison?
>> Do I survive?
>> Survive in prison.
>> You think so?
>> I think so.
>> I start [__] immediately. You have to
>> sucking immediately.
>> They will like him. They will have mad
respect for him,
>> for Tim, right? The way he is the way he
looks.
>> And they probably they know him.
>> Yeah.
>> They watch the Alex Jones episode.
>> You will see aliens this year, maybe
even this summer to go along with the
fun, but they're going to be government
scops. It's not. They look like aliens.
They'll appear like aliens, but it's
actually, you know, United States,
Russia, China making these things for
some type of global conspiracy according
to Alex Jones. Who knows? Well, hey.
>> Yeah,
>> it could happen.
>> Well, there here's the thing. If some of
them come down and start doing podcasts,
we're [__] If they want to do
podcast, if they want to start doing
standup, then there'll be no I mean,
what are some of these
>> I would like nothing more than to lose
my job to an extraterrestrial.
>> Yeah, that would be
>> Oh, imagine they get here and even
they're racist. How funny
they're they're picking the same sides.
I was like, "Oh, Jesus, that would
suck."
>> Like, you sit down, you're like, "All
right, so you're a higher dimensional
being. What do you have to say?" and you
go
Derek Schovin. You're like, "God, no.
God."
But we all going to New Orleans
>> and we meet at the cruise terminal and
many of the people that were taking the
cruise had decided to bring food and
beverages with them. So, automatically I
knew this was a
>> which you can't do, right?
>> Well, here's the thing. You can do it in
certain cases, but I knew this was a
group. So, bringing food and drinks on
vacation with you, that's a certain type
of person, you know? That's a certain
type of person. Let's be honest, that's
a disgusting person.
>> Yeah, it it is not for me. I'll tell you
that much. Not for me. So, I saw people
dragging coolers, all kinds of stuff.
Now, we're we're cruising into the
middle of theing ocean. But this boat is
the size of aing mall. It really is.
>> So, you'd imagine there'd be food on it,
but these people are like, "Just in case
that runs low, I have snacks."
>> Yeah.
>> So, for the room, one of the one of the
ladies said to me, I swear to God, she
goes, "I have brought snacks for the
room." I said, "For the room? There's a
24-hour buffet. Just to give you an
idea, these these people didn't want to
be caught in the room hungry. They
didn't want
me and Yiannis were talking about it.
There's not if if there's even a little
space in their stomach.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> If even a little bubble of air,
>> they fill it in.
>> They fill it in. I mean, you you see it
looks like you're at you looks like
you're at a fair watching a go-kart. It
looks like a go-kart festival. There's
just [__]
>> It's medieval times on the boat.
>> There's scooters everywhere. These
people are huge.
>> Dude, it is. Let me tell you right now,
it is crazy. I'm a big dude and I
understand that there's it's, you know,
there's a whole fat activist movement
where people are like, you know, you
should be fat. And I never was into
that. I was always like, I eat too I eat
too much. I should I should I eat so
much I can't go to sleep till 4 in the
morning till my food digest.
>> It's like this is not this is a bad
thing.
>> I'm slowly killing myself. When I used
to do cocaine for years and I never did
cocaine and thought about starting a
blog going, "Everybody get start doing
[__] up your nose. It's great. Everybody
should lay in bed till 4:00 a.m. and
with their throat all scratched."
>> You didn't feel discriminated against
when someone said, "Hey, you might want
to quit cocaine."
>> No. No.
>> And my oppressing me.
>> Yeah. I never So I I think food is like
a drug. You see people on this boat that
is their lifestyle.
>> Yeah. is GL like they're like like they
and they're not even and I hate to like
they're not even fat off good food.
>> You got fat off Pringles. Yeah.
>> And TV your TV dinner fat, your Arby's
fat, your buffet fat. Like you're not
you've never even had a good thing,
right?
>> They would come to New York. They would
have a stroke if they ate any of this
food. They'd be dead in a week. They
don't even know [__] like this exists.
They've never had proper tomato sauce or
anything. These are Domino's people.
Yeah. and they're on the boat and let me
tell you right now, man,
>> the kids are like little cinnamon buns.
>> They're huge.
>> The kids are huge. The kids are big.
Yeah,
>> the pool is the size of a postage stamp.
>> There's about two or three people that
can fit in this pool at once. Maybe one
person and her two children. And the
pool is completely full. I thought they
would have a big pool, water slide.
There's no water slide because everybody
keep getting stuck. You'd have to plunge
them out. Um, there was a buffet 24
hours two and this and the boat they
want to prevent an outbreak of disease.
So when you walk into the boat,
>> that's a nice friendly reminder every
time you [__] got to watch.
>> There's a Filipino guy cuz everybody who
works on the boat lives in the
Philippines.
>> This is the fact they're all the cruise
industry lives in the Philippines. You
never see them when they're not working.
They make them live in a pipe in the
middle of the ship. Okay?
>> And then they're allowed to come out
once a day. They're always working. You
never see them. He has talked about it.
You never there's no breaks. You never
see two cruise employees being like, you
know, you know, remember last crew? None
of that [__] Hard work. Hard at work or
they're gone. I don't know where they
are. Maybe they go overboard, but you
never see them.
>> They go back to the pipe.
>> So this one dude, he would just stand in
the front of the buffet and go washi and
he would spray your hands. And I'm
talking about this was not hand
sanitizer. This was like a [__] poison
like killing everything on you.
>> It hurt when he sprayed your hands. Like
it was like [__] ammonia that you had
to rub your hands. You rub the layer of
skin off your hands because everybody
was so they were so nervous about cuz
it's a petri dish. They're like we don't
want these people spread because if
there are cases where like 1,800 people
get sick and then the party's over.
>> Yeah. The Legionnaire disease nor virus.
Yeah.
>> Yeah. Then party's over. And what these
cruise lines do, Carnival crews will
abandon these [__] in the middle of
the ocean. They don't give a [__]
because none of these people are rich.
None of these people have lawyers. They
know they're not doing anything. So
Carnival's like, "Leave them out there."
And [__] Sometimes there's like a the
electrical griddle will go down on one
of these boats. And Carnival's like,
"Whatever. Just let the military of
whatever country figure it out." They
don't give a [__] cuz these people are
disposable. Carnival knows these [__]
don't have lawyers. They're not going to
come. This isn't a river cruise going
down the Dan. You know, these [__]
are going to deal with it. It is what it
is. Half of them won't notice, you know.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Wow.
>> I get on the boat. Yannis gets on the
boat. We start looking around and we
start saying to ourselves, we're looking
at all the the mouth breathers and they
have them in like a FEMA tent. They have
them in a big cruise terminal and they
got their food and their potato chips
and then they all start lumbering on
this thing and we're like, it just hits
us immediately. Oh, we're about to go
into the middle of the ocean
>> with Walmart. And that's exactly what it
is. That's what it is. And there's
nowhere to go. There's nowhere to go.
And listen, it's not a tropical par.
It's cold. You get out in the middle of
the ocean, you think it's like a
tropical paradise. It's people wearing
hoodies. It's kind of windy. It's not
that sunny. You dock at a shitty like uh
like a weird sandbar that Royal
Caribbean and Carnival Cruise bought and
have turned into Costa Maya Mexico,
which doesn't [__] exist. And it's
these guys that are dressed up like
concistadors and pirates and these
idiots. These fat idiots, they sell them
jewelry. There's a 24-hour news channel
in your little And by the way, the
accommodations you have, you stay in
like a little
>> I don't know how some of those people
fit in those cabins.
>> They They don't. They shut the door on
their fat. They tuck their It's like the
way that I fit into a jacket. They fit
into the cabin.
>> No, I want to ask you a serious
question. Put it down.
>> I don't want to bring them in.
>> What are you talking about? Why? Cuz you
don't want You look Look at her. She's
beautiful. She's pregnant. You look
glowing. Are you kidding me?
>> No, that's not true. You have a mother,
right? Isn't she a gorgeous woman? Women
in America now are supposed to be
morbidly obese. I don't know if you've
seen the internet, but
>> the goal is morbid obesity right now for
all women's and to be proud of it and to
inflict it on others.
>> Yes.
>> Can you just I just want to ask you
something into the mic. Now,
>> you know, Tim Vin, born and raised in
the, you know, Sunset Park, Bay Ridge
area. Real quick, I just want to know,
you don't have to name names, but I just
want to know, have you ever went on a
date with or, you know, hooked up with?
>> Am I gonna throw this at you?
>> No. somebody who you think was in the
mafia. The Italian mafia. Yes or no?
Have you ever went on a date with
somebody? No names. Who's who you think
has been in the Italian mafia?
>> You don't ask a woman that.
>> Well, have you?
>> We don't talk about this.
>> I just want to know because you've dated
some tough guys. How you know?
>> No,
>> you never have. That's a lie. I could
tell because because your nose ring is
quivering. That's a That's a [__]
lie.
>> So, how about MS13?
[Laughter]
>> Boulder Pass. When did Easy Pass come
out?
20 30 30 years. I mean, I feel like it's
always been out.
>> Look at Look at Tim. This is good
acting. This is the acting from Tim
right here.
>> Yeah.
>> Why did he volunteer that was
>> Oh, I don't know. Sherlock Holmes.
>> That was riddle me this.
>> I could I could feel your heart beating
faster right now. Like Daredevil.
>> It's this kind of acting that garnered
you the part in the horror film
Thanksgiving.
>> I made $3,500.
But you got the SAG health insurance.
>> Did they let you keep when they
decapitated you, they let you keep your
prosthetic head?
>> I have the head.
>> I wanted to ask the head.
>> That's awesome.
>> I gave it to President Trump.
>> Joe Rogan presented it for me to
President Trump.
>> Edit out our flaws and make us into a
higher being. And they think technology
go to you and go, "Your kid can have no
medical issues. No this, no that. And
and by the way, what about blue eyes,
blonde hair, or whatever." And it does
get Hitlerian and freaky and scary,
>> but it it does seem to be that is what a
lot of this
>> Well, I mean, one of the one of these uh
futurist said that they firmly 100%
believe this was an interview from last
year that the that the first human who
will live forever is alive right now.
They believe that.
>> That's right.
>> That who who will not whose
consciousness
>> and actually he's the president.
>> Not only not only is he alive,
>> what you do to help your mental health
in a positive way, do you do anything?
Do you have an affirmation or do you
meditate or do you walk? What do you do?
When I get anxious?
>> Yeah.
>> And when I feel like things aren't going
well for me and I feel like I'm, you
know, I'm feeling panicky, right?
>> You know what I mean? And this is
literally, and I'm recommending this to
everyone because, and I'm not jo I'm
like I'm not even kidding. And you go,
"Oh, he's gonna have a joke at the end
of this." But this I'm dead serious
about this. Literally,
when I
feel like I can't go on anymore,
I do something which people do and I I
didn't even know that it helped anxiety
and it's called heroin.
>> I do heroin.
>> Yes.
>> And it is so helpful to me because
you're in a state of euphoria. You
actually your eyes roll back in your
head
>> and you're kind of like not even on the
planet anymore and you feel like you're
floating
>> and it's been described as the most
intense orgasm you've ever had times a
million, right? Wow.
>> It's just endless feelings of euphoria,
true euphoria that you can't really get
from walking or meditating. You can't
get to there. Like a lot of people say
you can. They're full of [__] Heroin,
black, tart, china, white, whatever it
is, you have to shoot it and you can't
skin pop. Okay,
>> you have to mainline. So, you have to
find a vein
>> and then you have to inject it deep into
your vein.
>> Okay,
>> and and and but here's how good it is.
Halfway through the injection, you
>> it's over and then sometimes you don't
even have the strength to pull the
needle out of your hand.
>> So, you just kind of lay like that with
the needle and then you're like
with it.
>> Yeah.
>> So, I mean that's what I do.
>> That's what you do.
>> Mainline it deep in that vein. Um you
will truly get to a place that you've
never gotten to. Thank you for watching
this video right here on Joke World. And
make sure you press subscribe right now
for aroundthe-clock comedy news
coverage, including highlight videos
like this one, as well as exclusive
interviews with comedians and daily
shorts. And if you're a real nut job,
check us out on Patreon to unlock a new
universe of treasures for only five
bucks a month. For more free videos,
check out the end screen right after
this. And for free stickers, send us a
message on Instagram
>> joke.
Joke World
>> and the world is W RLD.
>> That's a great uh YouTube channel, Joke
World. Check it out.